The next point you're going to use for the lower legs especially is inner courtyard or stomach 44.
And this one is really easy to find, it's literally between the second and third toe.
So you're just going to rub in between the toes.
Just run your finger in there, massage in between the toes and this is another good one for dispersing pain, relaxing the muscles and dogs like to generally have their feet massaged by their owners, they don't like them touched by the vets much, but quite often they'll let the owners do just about anything.
You can do a full foot massage on them if you like.
There's good acupressure points in between the other toes as well, but this one specifically for muscle stiffness and pain in the back limbs.
So you'll want to work that one and again do both sides because quite often if this knee is hurting he's compensating by using this leg.
So you're causing discomfort and stiffness in both legs.
You want to work that point.
Again this is a massage, just rubbing that muscle between your fingers, the tissues between your fingers and really rub that fairly hard, feel that skin move around so that you know that you're getting some real movement in the area.